<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Stanton&#39;s Ramblings</title>
  
  
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://stantonwong.com/"/>
  <updated>2017-11-05T09:40:37.640Z</updated>
  <id>http://stantonwong.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Stanton</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Who am I?</title>
    <link href="http://stantonwong.com/2017/11/05/Who-am-I/"/>
    <id>http://stantonwong.com/2017/11/05/Who-am-I/</id>
    <published>2017-11-05T09:31:18.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-11-05T09:40:37.640Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I’ve been thinking about defining who I am on paper for awhile now.  I’ll do it in 4 pieces: a one sentence self-description, strengths, weaknesses, and interests. So here goes.</p><h3 id="If-I-was-to-define-myself-in-one-sentence"><a href="#If-I-was-to-define-myself-in-one-sentence" class="headerlink" title="If I was to define myself in one sentence:"></a>If I was to define myself in one sentence:</h3><p>“I am a generalist and logic focused jack of all trades type of person with an interest in creating more efficient systems that will benefit the world”. </p><h3 id="Strengths"><a href="#Strengths" class="headerlink" title="Strengths:"></a>Strengths:</h3><p>Long term planning, coming up with ideas, larger picture thinking, organizing and systemizing things, logic related tasks, open minded, comfortable with change, easily content.</p><h3 id="Weaknesses"><a href="#Weaknesses" class="headerlink" title="Weaknesses:"></a>Weaknesses:</h3><p>Lack of focus and easily distracted, constantly a little late (average of 8 minutes), easily find myself in a lazy and unproductive state, constant interrupter in conversations, not very good at caring about the people around me, slow to take action (often times because I’m not sure of my decision yet)</p><h3 id="Interests"><a href="#Interests" class="headerlink" title="Interests:"></a>Interests:</h3><p>Ways to improve our environment, ways to handle trash and recycling, alternative education, how to have a longer life, technology improvements, Japanese manga and good stories (both fiction and non-fiction), ways to connecting people to improve the world, the perfect government system, self improvement, why humans are the way they are, and most importantly, the cross section between all the previous interests and the future (I love thinking about the future).</p><p>If you have any feedback or additions to give me, please do. I’m especially looking for more weaknesses because I think it’s hard to be self critical sometimes and I value all criticism, especially if it’s with the intent of being constructive.</p><hr><p>Tomorrow’s piece will be my first ramble. My topics will come from my interests. The first ramble will be on “Why I think about the future”. </p><p>If you like it, let me know by giving me a like. If you have thoughts, comments, questions, grammar suggestions, or critiques on the writing or idea, give me a comment. Thanks for reading!</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;I’ve been thinking about defining who I am on paper for awhile now.  I’ll do it in 4 pieces: a one sentence self-description, strengths, 
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Starting to write</title>
    <link href="http://stantonwong.com/2017/11/05/Starting-to-write/"/>
    <id>http://stantonwong.com/2017/11/05/Starting-to-write/</id>
    <published>2017-11-05T09:29:20.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-11-05T09:32:18.101Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I’ve been wanting to get into the habit writing for a long time because I think written communication is a very valuable skill to have. A daily habit of writing would help me improve my writing ability and it will also give me an outlet for the tons of ideas I want to share. I haven’t because I’m lazy, scared, and am a perfectionist. These are all just excuses. Being lazy means that I haven’t made this a priority. Being scared means I’m afraid of how people see me if I put myself out there. And the perfectionist excuse is just a little bit of both being lazy and scared, </p><p>So starting today, I’ll be writing a short piece every day. These will be random ramblings of topics that I have encountered the day of or have been thinking about. To make sure I can get these out every day, the rule is to try and keep each piece short.</p><p>I’ll start by posting these on WeChat and Facebook.  If you like it, give me a like. If you have thoughts, comments, questions, grammar suggestions, or critiques, give me a comment.</p><hr><p>Tomorrow’s piece will be an honest introduction of me and what kind of topics I’ll be covering. Thanks for reading!</p>]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      
      
        &lt;p&gt;I’ve been wanting to get into the habit writing for a long time because I think written communication is a very valuable skill to have. A
      
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="writing" scheme="http://stantonwong.com/tags/writing/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
